W-What, w-what
Uh, w-what, w-what, what
Get clean, I'm dirty Get clean, I'm dirty
Hey, whoa, ya heard me  Hey, whoa
Get clean, I'm dirty  Get clean, I'm dirty
Hey, whoa, ya heard me  Hey, whoa, ya heard me
Get clean...
McGee 我现在不方便说话
McGee, I can't talk now.
-你在哪里 -我找到了Ferdinand Pisco
- Where are you? - Found Ferdinand Pisco.
我正在跟踪他
I'm following him now.
一个人吗 你应该打电话给我的
Alone? You were gonna call me.
是 我知道
Yeah, well, I understand that.
事发有些突然
Well, it happened kind of quick.
我们应该是合作的关系
We're supposed to be working together.
这家伙需要
This guy needs to be
低调处理
handled on the down-low.
坦白说 你在人群中挺显眼的
Frankly, you stick out in a crowd.
-那不是... -我得挂了
- That is not... - I got to go.
Yo, this the home of the Saints
Sinners in the streets, chrome on the Benz
The night life, we drink until we faint...
Whoadie, what it do
Louisiana L, but we never, never lose
Push it like weight, little mama keep movin'
We on Bourbon Street just foolin'
Gettin' po'd up till they ask, “What you doing”
Woop-woop, that's the sound of the police...
站住 联邦探员
Stop! Federal agent!
警察 不许动
Police! Don't move!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
GA字幕组
原创译制
翻译：飞姬、42殿、二f英
翻译：小范、二f英、兔姬
校对：师太、流年、风姬
总校：师太
字幕分配&统筹&时间轴：栗子
NCIS 新奥尔良
S03E14
嫌疑人身上都是血 带着这个
Suspect was covered in blood, armed with this.
声称是NCIS的人 但没有任何证明
Claimed he was NCIS, but no credentials.
说是在进行卧底工作
Said he was working undercover.
我把他拘留了
I had to take him into custody.
他是你们的人吗
Is he one of yours?
他们这样告诉我的
So they tell me.
-你做得对 Pete -谢谢
- You did the right thing, Pete. - Thanks.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
Pride
Pride.
我们在MTAC见过
We met over MTAC.
多重威胁警报中心 (Multiple Threat Alert Center)
Nick Torres
Nick Torres.
你给我留下的第一印象很深刻 Nick Torres
You make quite a first impression, Nick Torres.
来这座城市两小时不到 就被当作嫌疑人
Less than two hours in my city,and you get yourself arrested
拘留了
as a suspected murderer.
这可以算是某种纪录了吧
That's got to be some kind of record.
我可以解释
I got an explanation.
你和特别探员McGee
Yeah, you and Special Agent McGee
被派到新奥尔良取回被盗的情报 是吗
were sent to New Orleans to recover stolen Intel, yes?
是的 情报被称作恐袭剧本
Yes. It's called the Playbook.
汇总了多种
It's a collection of scenarios
针对美国的可行的恐怖袭击方案
for viable terrorist attacks against the U.S.
从国土安全部偷的 这个我知道
Stolen from Homeland Security. I... That much I know.
我不知道的是 你为什么在行动前
What I don't know is why you ran an operation
不先来报到
without checking in first.
在跟踪我做卧底时的前任联系人
Tracking down a former contact of my undercover days.
那可是这起谋杀案的受害者
That would be the murder victim.
Ferdinand Pisco 委内瑞拉特工
Ferdinand Pisco. Venezuelan operative.
他到城里是为了得到恐袭剧本
Uh, he's in town to acquire the Playbook.
必须处理地
Had to handle it, um...
谨慎
delicately.
啊
Ah.
那个词在华盛顿一定有不同的含义
That word must have a different meaning up in D.C.
但是在这里 在新奥尔良 在狂欢节上
But down here, in New Orleans, at Mardi Gras,
NCIS喜欢更低调些
NCIS likes to keep a lower profile.
Pride 我应该来报道的 这怪我
Pride, I was supposed to check in. That's on me.
但我做的只是跟着那家伙
But all I did was follow the guy.
杀他的另有其人
Someone else killed him.
很可能是为了确保
Probably to make sure
Ferdinand得不到恐袭剧本
Ferdinand didn't get the Playbook.
可能吧
Probably.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我们必须查出是谁
We have to find out who.
有个比较蠢的问题 呃
And here's a silly question... um...
你现在能解开我的手铐了吗
you think you could take these,uh, handcuffs off me now?
还没想好
Haven't decided yet.
Pride 我得告诉你
Pride, I'm telling you,
我的第二印象要比第一印象好得多
my second impression is so much better than the first.
希望如此
One can only hope.
Loretta
Loretta.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
我可不希望这样度过
This is not exactly how I expected to spend
狂欢节前的周末
the weekend before Mardi Gras.
估计Ferdinand Pisco
Imagine it wasn't how Ferdinand Pisco
也不希望这样度过
expected it would go either.
我认为等他感觉到受伤时
I don't think he even realized he was injured
已经太迟了
until it was too late.
就目前判断 只有一处刺伤
It's a single stab wound,as far as I can tell.
最短时间内造成的最大伤害
Maximum damage in minimum time.
-有凶手的线索吗 -有的
- Anything on the killer? - Oh, yeah.
找了多名目击者谈话
Spoke to multiple witnesses
他们都能肯定地指出嫌疑人
who positively I.D.'d the suspect.
不幸的是 他们描述的人就是他
Unfortunately,they all described him.
Nick Torres 你好
Nick Torres. How you doing?
我是Gregorio 但愿
I'm Gregorio. I'd be better if you had more
你有嫌疑人的更多信息 除了说"穿着小丑的衣服"
on the murder suspect than just“wearing a harlequin costume.”
真不好意思 我不知道
So embarrassing.I had no idea
穿成这样是这里流行的时尚
that was a common fashion statement here.
喜剧的克鲁
Krewe of Commedia.
主持新奥尔良狂欢节的民间组织
他们每年都会在这里举办聚会
They had their annual party here.
呃 什么人
Uh, crew of what now?
是新奥尔良的玩意儿 我现在也还不清楚
It's a New Orleans thing I'm still not clear on.
也就是说 昨晚有上百个
It means there were over a hundred Harlequins
穿成那样的小丑
dressed like that last night.
警方正尽力召集他们进行询问
NOPD's interviewing as many as they can round up.
能这样行凶的人一定早早就有了
Anyone who can kill like this had an escape route--
逃脱路线
long gone.
天啊 这太恶心了
Oh, man, that's so gross.
你发现了什么 Sebastian
What you got there, Sebastian?
死者的手机 很可能还有丙肝病毒
Victim's cell phone.And probably a case of hep C,
因为我刚检查完这个排水沟
considering this gutter I just pulled it out of.
我得回家 洗个
I'm gonna need to go home and take, like,
长长的"丝克伍"澡
a long Silkwood shower.
特指洗去环境带来的异味和污秽，源于凯伦・丝克伍事件
看上去被水浸坏了 你能恢复数据吗
Looks water damaged.Can you retrieve the data?
可以 我这就去
Oh, yeah, I'm on it.
Gregorio
Gregorio,
去查监控 我们需要了解
check surveillance.We need something more
凶手的更多信息 除了他看上去
on our killer other than he looks like
像这位Torres
Torres here.
-嗯 -所以 Ferdinand
- Mm-hmm. - So, Ferdinand
是来这里和偷恐袭剧本的人碰面
was here to meet up with whoever stole the Playbook.
关于那个人的身份有新消息吗
Any update on who that might be?
那是Mcgee负责的部分
That would be McGee's department.
Mcgee在哪里
Where's McGee?
外面太疯狂了
It is absolutely crazy out there.
Mcgee探员 终于来新奥尔良了
Agent McGee, finally in New Orleans.
你怎么样
How you doing?
还有你在这儿的第一个狂欢节怎么样
And your first Mardi Gras in the quarter.
我看你已经感染新奥尔良的氛围了
I see you've already caught on to the New Orleans vibe.
白天饮酒就是第一步
Day drinking is step one.
我没有喝酒
I-I am not day drinking.
有人硬塞给我的
Someone forced this into my hand.
是 你说了算 闪亮小伙儿
Yeah, if you say so, glitter boo.
不过 我确实是带着礼物来的
I do, uh, come bearing gifts, however.
我能用下你的电脑么
Can I use your computer?
当然
Absolutely.
我从一开始就一直在追踪偷恐袭剧本的人的
Been tracking the digital trail of whoever stole the Playbook
数字足迹
in the first place.
他们在这几天有些动作
They've been making some moves the last couple days.
是么 什么动作
Yeah? What kind of moves?
国安局关于恐袭剧本有了新发现
NSA's had an uptick in their chatter about the Playbook.
小偷正在网上拍卖它
Thief is putting it up for auction.
价高者得
It's going to the highest bidder.
来自全球各地的
So multiple bad actors
多个坏人想要出价
from all over the globe trying to make a bid.
Timothy McGee
Timothy McGee.
当成自己家
Make yourself at home.
-你好吗 -不错
- How are you? - Good.
早
Morning.
狂欢节中的新奥尔良
So, New Orleans at Mardi Gras
最适合这样的竞价
is perfect for an auction like this.
城中有上百万游客
Million visitors in the city,
一半都带着面具
half of them in masks.
进出都不容易被发现
Easy to slip in and out without being seen.
那咱们上街碰碰运气
Well, then let's hit the streets.
把恐袭剧本带回来
Let's get that Playbook back.
昨晚的事之后 你哪里都不要去了
Uh, you're not hitting anything after last night.
我主动出击联系了Ferdinand Pisco
Hey, I took initiative to contact Ferdinand Pisco.
行动失败不是我的错
I'm not the reason the operation went sour.
你要说服的不是我
I'm not the one you need to convince.
嗨 老大
Hey, boss.
对
Yeah.
他就在这
He's right here.
事实上 他想跟Pride说话
Actually, he wants to talk to Pride.
你还好吧 Dwayne
Are you holding up okay, Dwayne?
真希望国土安全部的麻烦
Wish Homeland's mess
没有在我们的后院失火 但是我们会解决的
hadn't ended up in our backyard, but we'll deal with it.
如果你想要 这里有支援
Got backup available if you want it.
更多的探员会带来更多的问题
More agents means more questions.
我想此事不要声张
I want to keep this contained.
那可就难了 国际特工的嫌疑人档案
That's gonna be hard to do. We've got a rogue's gallery
正在送来新奥尔良
of international operatives descending on New Orleans.
华盛顿的所有当局都想参与
Every agency in D.C. wants in.
我不久前
I just got through
才刚与FBI联手办过Javier Garcia的案子
hand-holding the FBI on the Javier Garcia case.
可不想再来个续集了
Don't need a sequel.
收到 我会进行干涉的
Roger that. I'll run interference.
谢了 Jethro
Appreciate it, Jethro.
你一向更会和管理层打交道
You always had a gentler way with the suits.
抱歉 刚刚不是在开玩笑吗
Sorry, that wasn't a joke?
叫Torres来
Send Torres in.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
好的 老大
You got it, boss.
-McGee -咋了 老大
- McGee. - Yeah, boss?
你脖子上的是什么东西
What is that around your neck?
哦 这些是串珠 是节日的东西
Oh, uh, they're beads. It's a festive thing.
想要融入...
Trying to get into the...
别管了
Never mind.
走错了
Wrong door.
我从Ferdinand Pisco的坏手机中
So I was able to retrieve data
恢复了数据
off of Ferdinand Pisco's busted cell phone.
-有什么线索 -短信
- What'd you get? - Texts.
他在跟偷恐袭剧本的人联系
He was, uh, communicating with whoever stole the Playbook.
他们本应在镇上见面的
They were supposed to meet in the Quarter.
对 有人在会面之前就杀了Pisco
Yeah, someone killed Pisco before the meeting took place.
从短信中能找到Pisco
Well, able to get us anything on Pisco
-或者小偷的线索么 -不行
- or the thief from the texts? - No.
但是我能追查手机的序列号
But I was able to trace the serial number from the phone,
这是几天前从一个机场小卖摊
and it was one of five burner phones
购买的五个一次性手机中的一个
purchased together at an airport kiosk a few days ago.
五个手机可能是五个买家
Five phones can mean five buyers.
我们只需要追踪手机 就能找到所有买家
All we have to do is track the phones, and we find all the buyers.
追踪手机可不简单
Tracking the phones isn't that easy.
你不能直接追踪信号塔的信号
Can't you just trace the ping from the cellular towers
进行三角定位之类的么
and triangulate or whatever?
不不 这都2017年了 Sonja
No, it's-it's 2017 now, Sonja.
基站定位的时代已经过去了
The era of the ping is long gone.
就连最便宜的一次性手机也装有GPS
Even cheap burner phones are GPS enabled.
真正的GPS追踪专家是Patton
You know, the real GPS tracking expert is Patton,
但他去给JSOC当网络安全顾问去了
and he's off consulting JSOC on some online security issue.
联合特种作战司令部(Joint Special Operations Command)
嘿 跟你们说 不是我吹牛
Hey, you know, uh, I don't mean to brag,
但我写过一个算法 算得上是卫星定位的
but I wrote an algorithm that is kind of a game changer
革新算法
in satellite circles.
-天呐 -你是
- Geez. - You're...
你是 你就是McGee 对吧
you're, uh... you're McGee, right?
呃 是我
Uh, yeah, yeah.
我叫Sebastian 我听说过你的很多故事
Yeah. I'm Sebastian. I-I've heard so much about you.
哦 是么
Oh, you have?
你一夜间从技术人员变成了特别探员
Well, you went from tech support to special agent overnight.
是FLETC的传奇啊
Sort of a legend at FLETC.
联邦执法培训中心(Federal Law Enforcement Training Center)
至少对我来说
At least, you know, to me.
那并没有那么简单
It-it wasn't quite that simple.
-不过 这个是简单的 -哦
- But, uh, this is. - Oh.
我来给你展示 你只需要
Let me show you this. All you need to do is
输入序列号
enter the serial numbers.
哇 这 这太神奇了
Whoa, this is, this is amazing.
这绝对不是刚体跟踪算法
There's no way that this is, uh, a rigid tracking algorithm.
不不不 刚体跟踪并不好 卫星电话
No, no, no. Rigid tracking's no good. Satellite phones
总在移动的 所以这个是
are always on the move, so this is
一个对地同步的步进追踪过程
a geosynchronous step track processing,
外加一点生动的设计
with a little bit of pizzazz on the side.
没错 对 完全明白了
Of course. Yeah, makes total sense.
哈 是吗
Ha. To who?
等一下 有一个手机刚刚开机了
Oh, wait. One of the burner phones just powered on.
在阿姆斯特朗公园附近
Somewhere near Armstrong Park.
我可以马上看到精确的位置
I'm getting the exact coordinates now.
很好
Nice.
有很多游客和一些醉鬼
Got a lot of tourists and a bunch of drunks.
不确定我们要找的是谁
Not sure who we're looking for.
有线索能帮到我们么 Sebastian
Any clues to help us out, Sebastian?
我只能告诉你 用那个手机的人
All I can tell you is that whoever is using
正在积极地发短信
that burner phone is actively texting right now.
我可能看到目标了
Well, think I see our target.
女士 我需要你转过身
Ma'am, I'm gonna need you to turn around,
把手举起来
put your hands in the air!
她死了
She's dead.
像Pisco一样被捅死了
Stabbed just like Pisco.
刚刚才发生的
It just happened.
是 凶手一定就在附近
Yeah, and whoever did it was just here.
据DNA显示 死者是Monica Grange
According to DNA, this is Monica Grange.
美国公民 化名加拿大人来旅游
U.S. citizen traveling under a Canadian alias.
因为跟一个叙利亚恐怖组织有关
Wanted in four different countries
被四个国家通缉
for ties to a Syrian terrorist group.
没错 待在暗中好些年 当中间人
Yeah, been off the grid for years acting as a middleman,
购买武器 情报 爆炸物
buying weapons, Intel, explosives.
可能在城里
Probably in town
准备购买恐袭剧本 就跟Ferdinand一样
to bid for the Playbook, just like Ferdinand.
还跟Ferdinand一样的是
And just like Ferdinand,
她在联系到那个卖家之前
she got stabbed before she could make contact
就被刺杀了
with whoever the seller is.
一天之内 两个特工在城里被杀
Two operatives in town murdered within a day.
凶手可能是另外的买家 想要干掉竞争者
Killer could be another buyer taking out the competition.
如果其他人都死了 讨价还价会简单一些
Easier to negotiate if everyone else is dead.
Sebastian和McGee正在追踪
Well, Sebastian and McGee are tracking down
剩下的一次性手机和买家
the remaining burner phones and buyers.
关于我们的凶手 我们只掌握了
Well, as for our killer, all we got is
嫌疑人昨晚逃跑的录像
footage of the suspect running away last night.
所以我们要怎么把恐袭剧本拿回来
So how do we get the Playbook back?
跟我说说吧
Talk to me.
Monica Grange死前正在跟凶手通信
Monica Grange was corresponding with the killer before she died.
他们本应在今晚见面
They were supposed to meet tonight.
我们有Monica的手机
We have Monica's phone.
我的身份是干净的 安排一次会面
I have a clean identity. Set up a meet.
我代替她出场
I'll go in in her place.
卖家一定会很谨慎
Seller's proven to be careful-- not gonna have
不会带着恐袭剧本去见面
the Playbook on him at the meeting.
如果不是女人出现 卖家可能会吓跑
Anyone but a woman shows up, seller could spook.
如果我作为Monica去呢
Well, what if I go in as Monica?
她一直待在暗中 也没有近照
I mean, she's been off the grid, no current photo.
卖家不会知道的
Seller will have no idea.
卖家会知道一切的
Seller will have every idea.
很抱歉 不过你带着警察的臭味
I'm sorry, but you reek of cop.
-你是想说我很难闻吗 -不 我是说
- You trying to say I smell? - No, I'm saying
卧底工作需要一定的天赋
that undercover work takes a certain flair.
就像你昨晚被逮捕的那种天赋吗
Like the flair you had last night when you got arrested?
哦 真的吗 我们要翻旧账吗
Oh, really? We're gonna do that?
听着 我只是想说
Look, all I'm trying to say is
如果我们想不动声色地把恐袭剧本拿回来
if we want to get the Playbook back quietly,
那我就是合适人选
then I'm your girl.
Gregorio说得没错
Gregorio's right.
学习Monica Grange的生活模式
Study up on Monica Grange
直到卖家出现
until the seller reaches out.
我得去验尸房了
I got to go to autopsy.
你发现了什么 Loretta
What'd you find, Loretta?
恐怕是这骇人的相似
Frightful symmetry, I'm afraid.
两个受害人都是被一刀刺入两根肋骨之间
Both victims killed with a single stab between the ribs...
直接刺穿心脏 很快就流血身亡了
...puncturing the heart, bled out within moments.
甚至没来得及意识到被刺
Probably didn't even realize they were stabbed
就已经太迟了
before it was too late.
武器的刀刃很薄
The weapon was thin-bladed.
很可能是短剑
Stiletto, most likely.
凶手是一个娴熟的专家 能够在人群中随意出入
Killer's a skilled expert who can slip in and out of a crowd
-还不被发现 -是的 没有留下任何纤维
- without being noticed. - Yeah, no sign of fibers,
以及DNA和指纹
DNA, fingerprints.
训练有素的情报探员吗
Trained intelligence agent?
或者是个刺客
Or an assassin.
无论凶手是谁 我们都得马上牵制住他
Whoever the killer is, we need to contain him now.
一个极度娴熟的刺客
A highly skilled assassin
漫步在狂欢节中的新奥尔良街头
roaming the streets of New Orleans at Mardi Gras.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
也许是时候该叫装甲部队了
Maybe it's time to call in the cavalry.
如果我们那么做了 来的就不只是FBI了
Well, if we do that, it won't just be the FBI coming.
-还会有CIA -对啊 那些人太恶心了
- Be CIA, too. - Yeah, and those guys suck.
是啊 会像西大荒一样
Yeah, it'll be like the Wild West.
尤指尚无法制的美国西部
不能让这事发生  Sebastian
Can't let that happen. Sebastian,
告诉我你有好消息
tell me you got good news.
McGee和我黑进了最后三个手机
McGee and I were able to hack the last three burner phones.
也就是说我们可以追踪它们的位置了
Means we can track their locations.
是啊 不过 我们可以做得更好
Yeah, well, we can do better than that.
我们可以把买家引过来
We're gonna draw the buyers to us.
伪装成卖家 给他们发信息
Send them text messages, pretending to be the seller,
然后把他们清理干净 经典的请君入瓮行动
then sweep them up-- classic false flag operation.
那是什么意思 具体点
And what does that mean, exactly?
我也不知道 McGee这么说的
I have no idea-- something that McGee said.
但是听起来真的很酷 对吧
But it sounds really cool, right?
Chris Sonja
Chris, Sonja,
帮助McGee和Sebastian把买家吸引过来
help McGee and Sebastian bring in the buyers.
记住 他们之中可能会有那个凶手
And remember, any one of them could be our killer.
需要你们谨慎行动
Need you to proceed with caution.
明白
You got it.
这是国际刑警组织
That's the entirety
关于Monica Grange的全部文件
of Interpol's file on Monica Grange.
勉强一页纸
It's barely a page long.
只好将就一下了
It'll have to do.
她是个专业律师
She's a lawyer by profession,
所以你得假装你懂法律
so you're gonna have to pretend like you understand law.
不用假装
Don't need to pretend.
我就是律师 加入FBI以前上过法学院
I am a lawyer; went to law school before joining the FBI.
她会说一口流利的阿拉伯语
She's fluent in Arabic.
我猜你不会
I'm assuming you're not.
不会 但是我曾经
No, but I dated
跟一个埃及人约会过 学过一两个句子
an Egyptian once and learned a phrase or two.
要知道 作为一个从未做过卧底的人
You know, you're pretty cocky
你相当自负啊
for someone that's never worked undercover before.
哦 我曾经参与过卧底任务
Oh, I've worked undercover ops before.
好吧 但我说的可不是那种 花几天时间
Yeah, well, I'm not talking about a couple of days
获取信任
of playing make-believe,
拿下毒贩的小把戏
take down a drug dealer.
我说的是
I'm talking about
作为另一个人 生活好几年
spending years being another person.
时间长到让你
So long that you...
让你忘记自己真正是谁
you forget who you really are.
很有意思
Fascinating.
但是我只需要一两个小时 拿到恐袭剧本 所以...
But all I need is an hour or two to get the Playbook back, so...
而你只需要搞砸一次
And all you need is to screw up once,
整个形势就会变得极其严峻
and this entire situation goes pear-shaped.
你知道 我的阿拉伯语可能不流利
You know, I may not be fluent in Arabic,
但我对肢体语言很熟悉
but I am fluent in body language,
让你坐板凳简直要了你的命
and it's killing you to ride the bench.
让我坐板凳确实很要命
It's killing me to ride the bench.
你知道 我是坐不住的人 我是个喜欢外勤任务的人
You know, I'm not a bench guy; I'm an on-the-field kind of guy.
不是很喜欢团队行动 哈
Not much of a team player, huh?
没错 这种 呃
No, this, uh...
团队的事情 我是近来才参与的
team thing has been pretty recent.
这需要调整
It's an adjustment.
我明白 作为一个新人 加入到
I get it. It's not easy being the new guy
一群共事很久的人中间 很不容易
with a group that's worked so long together.
没错 比如说他们内部才懂的笑话...
Yeah, I mean, inside jokes alone...
是啊 而且你无法完全确信
Yeah, and you're never fully confident that
他们真的需要你 那感觉就像 我这是在做什么呢
they actually need you, right? It's, like, what am I doing?
没错
Exactly.
但是我需要你 Torres
Well, I'm gonna need you, Torres,
因为我完全不知道我在做什么
'cause I have no idea what I'm doing.
我们从那儿开始 好吗
So let's just start there, all right?
这是卖家
It's the seller.
8点会面
Meeting's at 8:00.
Sazerac酒吧
Sazerac Bar.
我会告诉Pride
I'll let Pride know.
不应该这么做 Sebastian
Not gonna want to do that, Sebastian.
眼睛往前看 或者看我
Keep your eyes forward or on me.
好吧 那 那我们怎么知道目标什么时候出现呢
Well, how-how will we know when the target's here?
窗户玻璃的反射
Window reflections.
在那安装了安全反射镜
Got a security mirror up there.
大约还有五种方法可以知道我们身后发生了什么
There's about five other ways to know what's going on behind us.
怎么了 我的头发里还有亮片吗
What, I still got glitter in my hair?
不是
No.
还是有的 但不是这个问题
Well, yeah, but that's not it.
你跟我一样是个书呆子 你知道吗
You're a nerd like me, you know?
但你是那种了不起的书呆子
But you're, like,this badass nerd.
你很擅长这些
You're so good at this.
只是有更多的经验
Eh. Just have more experience.
不是的 你让这事看起来很容易
No, you-you make it look easy.
我却只会把事情搞砸
I just keep messing up.
听着
Look...
当我是个菜鸟的时候 我也总是会搞砸
when I was a probie,I messed up all the time.
我犯过非常多错误
Okay? I made a ton of mistakes.
但我很幸运 我有几位至关重要的导师
But I was fortunate;I had some key mentors
手把手地教我
that showed me the ropes.
那么他们肯定非常有耐心 还很宽容
Well, they must have been very patient and forgiving, then.
他们很不讲情面 有时候还很刻薄
They were merciless. Downright mean sometimes.
但是你知道吗
But you know what?
他们总是为我殿后 我也总为他们殿后
They always had my six,and I always had theirs.
买家到了
Buyer's here.
短上衣 猎鸭靴
The windbreaker,duck boots.
没错
All right.
好了 我要把他引到小巷子 远离人群
All right, I'll send him out to the alley away from everyone,
-这样我们能在那把他抓住 -好的
- so we can pick him up there. - All right.
-好了 你这边 我这边 -现在干嘛 什么意思
- All right, you zig, I zag. - What, now? What's that?
-跟着他 -好的
- Follow him. - Okay, yeah, all right.
你好 呃
Hi. Uh...
我是联邦探员
I'm a federal agent...
停止抵抗
Stop-stop resisting.
停止抵抗 就会没事的
Stop resisting. It's gonna be okay.
只要
Just...
我们都会没事的
We're all gonna be fine.
什么招数 类似什么神经阻断术吗
What was that, like, a...like, a Vulcan nerve pinch?
摩萨德手法 我的一个老朋友教我的
Mossad technique an old friend of mine taught me.
摩萨德全称：以色列情报和特殊使命局
好了 我们得把他弄起来 拖到车里
All right, we got to get him up here, get him in the car.
好的 没问题
Yeah. No problem.
好的
Okay.
希望我们没有把车停得很远
Kind of wish we didn't park so far away.
加油
Come on.
? I've cussed on a Sunday ?
? I've cheated and I've lied ?
? I've fallen down from grace ?
? A few too many times ?
? But I find holy redemption ?
? When I put this car in drive ?
? Roll the windows down ?
? And turn up the dial... ?
这里挤满了人
It's packed in here.
我们会更容易隐蔽
Easier for us to stay hidden.
但如果出了问题就太拥挤了
But too crowded if there's a problem.
我应该跟你一起进去的
I should be in there with you.
待在原地 Torres
Stay where you are, Torres.
万一情况有变 你是我们的后援
You're our backup,in case things go south.
我会没事的
I'll be okay.
? I find my soul revival ?
? Singing every single verse... ?
给你的 女士
For you, miss lady.
-哦 我没有点这些 -我点的
- Oh, I didn't order these. - No, I did.
一起吗
Join me?
那是卖家还是个诱饵
That the seller or just a come-on?
她是卖家
She's the seller.
Eva Azarova
Eva Azarova.
俄罗斯的潜伏间谍
Russian sleeper agent.
去年算是有帮我们摆脱困境
Sort of helped us out of a mess we were in last year.
算是
Sort of?
那个麻烦起初正好是
She happened to be responsible for the mess
-她负责 -我的习惯是
- in the first place. - I make it a rule
不喝陌生人的酒
not to take drinks from strangers.
你永远不知道里面有什么
You never know what's in it.
嗯 我认为酒不是你需要担心的
Mm. I don't think it's the drink you need to worry about.
你不如告诉我 你到底是谁
Why don't you tell me exactly who you are.
? Can I get a hallelujah... ?
我是Monica Grange
I'm Monica Grange.
你应该知道 因为是你邀请了我
You should know that because you invited me.
该来的总会来 哪怕藏得再深
是阿拉伯语
That's Arabic.
Monica很流利 Gregorio不行
Monica's fluent. Gregorio's not.
我要出手了 Pride
Counts as sideways to me, Pride.
等等 Torres
Hold on, Torres.
不是你的终究不是你的 哪怕到了你的嘴边
不要让过去的伤痛封闭你...
...追求新生的心
不知道这句话 很优美
Don't know that saying. It's beautiful.
是什么意思
What does it mean?
意味着你不是唯一一个带着武器的
It means you're not the only one who came armed.
可能会出事 Torres
Might have an issue, Torres.
可能需要你去守住前门
Might need you to cover the front door.
我们不要闹事
Let's not cause a scene.
放松一下 品尝我们的酒
Let's relax and enjoy our drinks.
给我点时间 你也会喜欢和我在一起
Give me some time, you'll enjoy the company as well.
? My church. ?
先生们女士们 为Maren Morris鼓掌
Give it up for Maren Morris, ladies and gentlemen.
美国乡村歌手 作曲家 制片人
Pride确认了
Pride got a positive I.D.
偷恐袭剧本的嫌疑人身份
on the suspect who stole the Playbook.
很好
Good.
Eva Azarova吗
Eva Azarova?
我以为我们去年因间谍活动把她抓起来了
I thought we put her away last year for espionage.
是的 猜她是逃了出来 不知怎么得到了剧本
Yeah. Guess she escaped,somehow got the Playbook.
现在她正设法把它卖了
Now she's trying to sell it.
Gregorio与她取得了联系
Gregorio's made contact.
希望她能把恐袭剧本拿回来
Well, hopefully, she gets the Playbook back
在更多人受到伤害之前
before anyone else gets hurt.
对 与此同时 我们已经
Yeah. Meanwhile, we've got
拘留了三名国外买家中的两名
two out of the three foreign buyers in custody.
尽管他们并不说话
Though ours isn't talking.
对啊 是朝鲜特工
Yeah, North Korean operative.
就坐在那儿 好像他听不懂我们在说什么
Just sits there like he doesn't understand a word we're saying,
微笑 点头
smiling and nodding.
你们的进展顺利吗
You guys have any better luck?
没有 不过
No. Although, oh, man,
你们应该去审讯室
you guys should've been in interrogation
看看McGee是怎么工作的
to see McGee go to work.
他一直没有说话
He did this whole no-talking thing
把我们的罪犯吓坏了
that completely freaked our guy out.
他最终告诉了我们他的所有故事
I mean, he ended up telling us his entire
就是为了让McGee开口说话
life story just to get McGee to speak.
真酷
So cool.
怎么了
What?
你真的喜欢McGee 是吗
You really like McGee,don't you?
是啊 我觉着有点男人间的欣赏
Yeah, bit of a man crush,you ask me.
对 就是男人间的欣赏
It's a total man crush, yeah.
而且 这就像看一个水晶球
Also, it's like looking into a crystal ball
看看我将来可能的样子
to see what I could potentially become.
你们知道吗 McGee基本上就是未来的Sebastian
You know? I mean, McGee is basically future Sebastian.
好吧 未来的Sebastian现在在哪里
Well, where's future Sebastian now?
他在Patton的办公室 正试着追踪最后一个手机
He's in Patton's office trying to track the final burner phone.
但目前还没有进展
No luck so far, though.
手机甚至都没有开机
It hasn't even been turned on.
另外两个买家被谋杀了
Well, two of the other buyers were murdered,
也许另外一个有手机的人也死了
so maybe whoever has the other phone is dead, too.
或者他可能是
Or he could be
凶手 开始争夺恐袭剧本
the killer, take out the competition for the Playbook.
关于凶手
Well, all we know
我们只知道他穿着狂欢节的服装
about the killer is that he was wearing a Mardi Gras costume,
以及他擅长用刀 我们需要更多信息
and he's good with a knife. I mean, we need more.
我也一直在做这件事
Well, that's what I've been working on.
我们有Ferdinand Pisco被杀当晚
So, we have about ten seconds of surveillance video
大概十秒钟的监控视频
from the night Ferdinand Pisco was killed.
我在用一个特殊的电脑程序
I'm using a special computer program
来分析嫌犯的步态
to analyze the suspect's gait--
步幅 身高 尺寸
stride length, height, measurements.
-甚至可以推测性别 -这是真的吗
- It can even predict gender. - Is this for real?
我会交叉比对我们的数据库
I'm gonna cross-check the results against our database,
希望能找到一个靠谱的嫌犯
and hopefully come up with a viable suspect.
好的 加油干吧 过去的Sebastian
Yeah, well, keep at it, Past Sebastian.
没错
Yeah.
鉴于你的身份
You're not at all what I was expecting,
你跟我预期的样子不太一样
given who you represent.
? Oh, baby, we go together... ?
以为会穿着套装 拿着公文包么
Looking for a pantsuit and briefcase?
或者是 戴个眼罩来道疤
Or maybe an eye patch and a scar?
我不知道
I don't know.
就是不像你
Just not you.
嘿 Gregorio
Hey, Gregorio,
你觉得你应该尽快提出恐袭剧本的事情
you think you might bring up the Playbook anytime soon,
还是像第二次约会一样
or is that a like a second date
有问有答
type of question?
对我失望了吗
Do I disappoint?
一点都没有
Not in the least.
说真的 Pride
Honestly, Pride, how long
这前戏我们要玩多久
are we gonna go on with the foreplay?
Gregorio 你也许该推一下进度了
Gregorio, you might want to give her a push.
好了 我们谈正事吧
Well, let's talk business.
我的雇主希望能尽快出个价
My employer is eager to make an offer.
我还没想好自己对出价是否感兴趣
I haven't decided if I'm entertaining an offer.
那我还能做点什么来说服你呢
Well, what else do I have to do to convince you?
在电梯里见我
Meet me at the elevator.
我们要去哪
Where are we going?
我的房间 带着你的酒
My room. And bring your drink.
因为这是唯一能让你看到恐袭剧本的办法
'Cause it's the only way you're gonna get to see the Playbook.
我会非常规矩的
I'll be on my best behavior.
我保证
Promise.
? But I wish, but I wish I was ?
? Ooh, I wish, oh, wish I was... ?
我要过去了 哥们
I'm heading up, boys.
如果苗头稍有不对 Gregorio
One sideways glance, Gregorio,
我们就立即终止整个行动
we shut this whole operation down.
请把武器放在桌子上
Weapon on the table, please.
你也是
You, too.
嗯
Hmm.
顶层套房
Penthouse.
能看到整个街区 很不错
View of the Quarter. Very nice.
十楼 酒店东侧
Tenth floor, east side of the hotel.
你一发话 我就行动
You say the word, I'm on the move.
我订这个房间不是为了风景
I didn't book the room because of the view.
阳台能让我上到楼顶
Balcony gives me access to the roof.
必要时候 是一条逃生路线
Escape route if I need it.
偏执的生活方式
Paranoid way of life.
我们这行生存的方式
Only way to survive in our line.
但很累人
Gets tiring, though.
为什么干这个呢
Why do it?
我有我的原因
I've got my reasons.
这就是恐袭剧本
Here's the Playbook.
语音激活的安全系统 需要我的声音
Voice activation security needs my voice.
祸不单行
看看吧
Have a look.
-Sebastian -Pride
- Sebastian. - Pride.
我运行的步态分析软件 刚刚得到一个匹配结果
I just got a hit back on that gait analysis I was running.
什么是步态分析软件
What's gait analysis?
现在解释这个太复杂了
It's too complicated to explain right now.
简单说 我们查出了谋杀嫌犯的身份
Bottom line, we got an I.D. on our murder suspect.
匹配结果是Eva Azarova
Eva Azarova came back as a match.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
程序不是百分百精确
Program's not 100% accurate,
但是 没错 我非常确定
but, yeah, I'm-I'm pretty damn sure.
Torres
Torres,
Gregorio跟凶手在一起
Gregorio's up there with our killer.
我去房间
I got the room.
你殿后
You cover the back
以免她试图逃跑
in case she tries to escape.
收到
Copy.
Gregorio 你听到了吗
Gregorio, do you hear that?
已经确定Eva是
Got confirmation that Eva's responsible
谋杀Ferdinand的凶手
for Ferdinand's murder.
我正在赶过去 但你得马上离开那里
I'm on my way, but you need to get out of there now.
一切看起来都没问题 我会联系我的雇主
Everything seems in order. I'll reach out to my employer...
我知道你不是Monica Grange
I know you're not Monica Grange,
因为我今早看着她死了
because I watched her die this morning.
我以为可能是Victor派你来的
I thought Victor may have sent you
因为你绝对是他喜欢的类型
because you're definitely his type.
我完全不知道Victor是谁 但你要面临一个更大的问题
I don't even know who Victor is, but you got bigger problems
因为你正用刀子指着一个联邦探员
'cause you're pointing a knife at a federal agent.
扔掉它
Drop it!
马上
Now!
Pride 嫌犯已经在我控制之下
Pride, I got the suspect in custody.
收到 马上就到
Copy that. Almost there.
Pride
Pride?
你是NCIS的人
You're NCIS.
没错
Yeah.
你因为间谍行为以及
And you're under arrest for espionage
谋杀Ferdinand Pisco和Monica Grange被捕了
and the murder of Ferdinand Pisco and Monica Grange.
你们在间谍这事上确实抓到我了 可我没杀那两个人
Well, you got me on espionage, but I didn't kill those people.
哦 是吗 那谁杀的
Oh, yeah? Then who did?
刚刚做了这个的人
Same person who just did that.
-你受伤了吗 -没有
- You hit? - No.
待在那
Stay there.
Gregorio
Gregorio?
你还好吗
You okay?
两个枪手跑出了阳台
Two gunmen went out the balcony.
他们拿着恐袭剧本
They have the Playbook.
Torres 两个嫌犯朝你那里去了 有武装
Torres, two suspects headed your way, armed.
Torres 你收到了吗
Torres, do you copy?
Torres探员现在无法回应你
Agent Torres is unable to respond.
你是谁
Who is this?
这是一个要跟你谈判的人
The man you'll be negotiating with
如果你想让Torres活着回来的话
if you want Torres back alive.
问问Eva 如果你不服从 会有什么后果
Ask Eva what happens if you don't comply.
我等你的电话
I'll expect your call.
刚跟Vance主任通完电话
Just got off the phone with Director Vance,
他正准备派陆战队员来救Torres回去
who's ready to send the Marines down to get Torres back.
-我们现在掌握多少 -不太多
- What do we know? - Not much.
Torres和恐袭剧本昨晚被三个持枪者
Torres and the Playbook were taken last night
装进一辆黑色SUV 从Roosevelt酒店带走了
by three gunmen in a black SUV at the Roosevelt Hotel.
Sebastian和McGee正在尝试追踪那辆SUV的移动路线
Sebastian and McGee are trying to track the movements
但是看起来它就那么凭空消失了
of that SUV, but it seems like it vanished into thin air.
不论这个Victor是谁 他对自己做的事非常拿手
This Victor's good at what he does, whoever he is.
Eva像是明确知道他是谁
Well, Eva seems to know exactly who he is.
她昨晚像是在等他
It's like she was expecting him last night.
他可能就是第五个买家
He could be the fifth buyer,
是他杀死了其他买家
responsible for killing the others.
是啊 昨晚在酒店里守株待兔
Yeah, laying in wait at the hotel
等着抢走恐袭剧本
last night to grab the Playbook.
但是Ferdinand Pisco和Monica Grange被杀时
But Eva was there when Ferdinand Pisco
Eva在场 为什么
and Monica Grange were killed. Why?
这有一堆没法回答的问题
It's a lot of unanswered questions.
比如说 Torres还活着吗
Like, is Torres even still alive?
Torres还活着 因为Victor要把他当筹码
Torres is alive because Victor needs him as a bargaining chip.
好吧 没有Eva的语音识别
Well, Playbook can't be opened
恐袭剧本没法被打开
without Eva's voice verification.
Eva是那个有可能为我们
And Eva's the one person who might be able to fill in
解开谜团的人 Gregorio我们走
the rest of the blanks for us. Let's go, Gregorio.
继续查
Keep digging.
我希望我那位新朋友能加入我们
I was hoping that my new friend would join us.
没能知道她的真名
I didn't catch her real name.
真是太遗憾了
That's too bad.
绝对没猜到她是一名联邦探员
Never would have guessed that she was a federal agent.
而且 她打起架来 很有一手
Plus, she has a mean right hook.
我会转告她的
I'll let her know.
现在 你得告诉我Victor是谁
Right now, you need to tell me who Victor is.
俄罗斯探员
Russian agent,
恶毒的杀手
vicious assassin,
我的导师
my mentor.
我的一切都是他教的
Taught me everything I know.
我们认为他犯下了
We think he's responsible...
这两起谋杀
for these two murders.
真是似曾相识 Eva
Here we are again, Eva.
是的
Yup.
你指控我没有犯过的罪
You're accusing me of crimes I didn't commit.
但你的确犯罪了
But you did commit a crime.
你从国土安全部偷了恐袭剧本
You stole the Playbook from Homeland.
卖给价高者
Sell to the highest bidder.
没想到你是一个投机取巧的人
Never pegged you as an opportunist.
你说对了
You're right.
我本打算把这当作诱饵 引Victor出现
I was using it as bait to draw Victor out.
你的导师
Your mentor.
他在我还是个孩子的时候招收了我
He recruited me when I was just a child.
他把我从我家里带走
He took me from my family.
他让我做一些 非常糟糕的事情
He made me do...terrible things.
他把我变成了这样
He turned me into this.
没有国家的女人
Woman without a country.
我看到了一个报复他的机会
I saw an opportunity to pay him back,
因为我知道他会为了恐袭剧本
'cause I knew that he would come crawling out
从藏身之处跑出来的
from under his rock if the Playbook was up for grabs.
这个诱惑太大了
It's too big a prize.
然后我就能报仇了
And then I would have justice.
你的复仇计划害死了两个人
Two people are dead because of your justice.
Victor拿到了恐袭剧本
Victor has the Playbook
以及我们的一名探员
and one of our agents.
你需要我去救他回来
You need me to get him back.
用我去换你的探员
Trade me for your agent.
然后我们会一起抓住Victor
And we'll take Victor down together.
问题是 你目前的表现
Well, problem is, the way you've acted...
我不知道该怎么信任你
don't know how I can afford to trust you.
你必须得相信我
How can you afford not to?
不确定能不能相信Eva说的话
Not sure we can take Eva at her word.
当然不能
I'm sure we can't.
我知道她的那个眼神
I know that look in her eyes.
-她一意孤行想要报仇 -我懂的
- She's hell-bent on revenge. - I get it.
如果在我前夫干了那些混蛋事之后
If I had a chance to take down my ex-husband
有机会能扳倒他 没有什么能阻止我
after all the crap he pulled, nothing would stop me.
我们得有个备用计划去救Torres 取回恐袭剧本
We need a plan B to get Torres and the Playbook back safely.
McGee和我可能有你想要的东西
McGee and I might have what you're looking for.
嘿
Hey.
-嘿 -拿到了
- Hey. - Got footage
Victor的SUV昨晚离开酒店的监控录像
of Victor's SUV leaving the hotel late last night.
-在那辆车消失之前么 -事实上 它没消失
- Before it disappeared into thin air? - Actually, it didn't.
SUV在逃离现场时
The SUV passed a number of cameras
路过了一系列的摄像头
while it fled the scene.
是的 交通摄像头 安保摄像头
Yeah, traffic cameras, security cameras,
路人的个人记录仪
pedestrians' personal cameras...
如果我们能拿到这些录像
If we can access that feed,
就能拼凑出SUV到底去哪里了
we can piece together exactly where the SUV went.
我们没有这样的资源
We don't have the resources
为了找一个单一目标
to consolidate footage from
去整合那么多资源
dozens of sources to find a single target.
国安局有
The NSA does.
这案子关系到国家安全
This case involves national security
以及国际间谍
and international espionage.
我让Bishop找她的老领导帮了些忙
I asked Bishop to call in some favors from her old bosses.
是的 我们在这儿追踪SUV
Yeah. We track the SUV from here.
Lasalle和Percy 在我们整合情报的期间
Lasalle and Percy, they're our boots on the ground
在外面跑腿
while we gather Intel.
我们一定会找到Torres的
We're-we're gonna find Torres.
这事儿合法嘛
How legal is this, guys?
严格地说 我们进入了一些灰色地带
Well, strictly speaking, we're entering a bit of a gray zone.
我的一个队员被一个反社会的俄罗斯探员带走了
One of my team was taken by a sociopathic Russian agent.
管它什么灰色地带
I say screw the gray zone.
我们同意你 McGee
We're with you, McGee.
如果这方法能救回Torres
If it'll get Torres back,
去做吧
get after it.
我们得给他们更多的时间
We need to buy them more time.
Victor不会无所事事坐以待毙的
No way Victor's sitting around, waiting to get caught.
在我们找他的期间 只有一个办法让Victor忙起来
Well, there's only one way to keep Victor occupied
我们得把Eva放出来加入游戏
while we search for him: we need to put Eva into play.
我会给Torres打电话
I'll call Torres's phone.
看我是否能和Victor联系上
See if I can make contact with Victor.
我还以为你不会打电话了呢
I was beginning to lose hope you'd ever call.
Torres探员也这么以为
So was Agent Torres.
-他还好吧 -他没事
- Is he all right? - He's fine.
我会放他回去 以交换我的特工
I'll let you have him back in return for my agent.
你想要Eva回来的唯一原因 是要打开恐袭剧本
The only reason you want Eva back is to access the Playbook.
Torres命在旦夕的时候 这真的重要么
Does it really matter, with Torres's life on the line?
我想和他说话
I want to speak to him.
说话
Speak.
Pride
Pride.
你还好吧 Nick
You okay, Nick?
这里的干墙让我起过敏反应了
Well, my allergies are acting up 'cause of all this drywall,
但从这里能看到游行队伍
but the view of the parade route from here,
-呃... -别给提示 Torres探员
- it's, uh... - No hints, Agent Torres.
就说你很好
Just say you're fine.
我很好
I'm fine.
我会发消息告知 你们把Eva带到哪里去交易
I'll send a text where to bring Eva for the trade.
一旦我有了她 我会告诉你们Torres在哪里
Once I have her, I'll tell you where Torres is.
不不不 我们得做一个公平的交易
No, no, no, no. We do an even trade.
没什么条件可谈的
Terms are non-negotiable.
这事儿有五十种可能会崩
There's 50 ways this goes south.
真是乐观 我能想到一百种可能
That's optimistic. I can think about 100.
他想让我们
He wants us at
20分钟后去Huey P. Long桥
the Huey P. Long Bridge in 20 minutes.
不要耍花招 按着计划来
Keep this very simple, and you don't go off book.
明白吗
Understand?
Victor不会按计划来的
Victor's gonna go off book.
他会背叛你们 这是他会做的事情
He's gonna double-cross you. That's what he does.
是啊 所以我们有这追踪装置
Yeah, well, that's why we have the tracking device.
密切监视Victor
Keep tabs on Victor.
我还以为 你只是
Here I was thinking you were just
为非礼我找了个借口
looking for an excuse to get fresh.
Lasalle 有新消息吗
Lasalle, what's the update?
有好消息也有坏消息
Good news and bad news.
Sebastian和McGee找到了
Sebastian and McGee were able to track down
Victor的SUV的最终位置
Victor's SUV till its final destination.
-你看到了 -是的
- You got eyes on it? - Yeah.
它停在市中心一栋废弃大厦的外面
It's parked outside an abandoned building in the CBD.
坏消息是啥
Bad news?
大厦有30层高
Well, the building's 30 stories tall.
Torres可能在里边 也可能不在
Torres might be inside, and he might not.
在不惊动俄罗斯人的情况下 得费些时间去搜查
It's gonna take time to search without alerting the Russians.
没错 但我们没什么时间了
Yeah, well, time's something we're running out of.
开始找吧
Start searching.
我对这事不是很有信心
I don't know about all this.
什么 你害怕抓捕那些可能武装到牙齿的
What, you worried about taking on some Russian spies
俄罗斯间谍么
who are probably armed to the teeth?
不 但我讨厌台阶 看来我们
No. But I hate stairs, and looks like we're about
得爬好多节楼梯
to take on a crapload of them.
让Eva一个人过来
Send Eva alone.
你们俩站在原地
Two of you stay where you are.
按他说的做
Do what he says.
做好干掉他的准备
Be ready to take him out.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
Eva 好久不见
Eva, it's been too long.
该我们了
Our turn now!
Torres在哪里
Where's Torres?
我们安全离开后 我会发短信告诉你们地址
Once we're safely away, I'll text you the address.
迫不及待想见你了
Can't wait to catch up with you.
注意你的行为
Play your cards right,
你刚从这混乱中幸存下来
you just might survive this mess.
但你不会 Victor
But you will not, Victor.
你刚才到底做了什么
What the hell did you just do?
做了我一直想做的事
Something I've been waiting for a long time.
你刚杀了唯一一个
You just killed the one person
能帮我们找回Torres的人
who could help us get Torres back.
你耍了我们 Eva
You really screwed us here, Eva.
Victor的手下正在等他的电话
Victor's guys are waiting for his call.
现在他们会杀Torres的
Now they'll kill Torres.
他迟早会杀了Torres的 我刚才帮了你们
He would've killed Torres anyway. I did you a favor.
-怎么会 -我帮你们拖延了时间
- How's that? - I bought you time.
一旦我们离开
He would've slit
他会立即割掉你们探员的喉咙
your agent's throat the minute we pulled away.
等等 Lasalle和Sonja已经接近
Wait, Lasalle and Sonja are already
Victor的藏身点了 我们得联系他们
near Victor's hideout. We need to call them
给他们具体地址 这样他们才能救出Torres
and give them the exact location so they can rescue Torres.
我有个主意
I got an idea.
但我们还得让她帮忙
But we're gonna need her help again.
Victor 怎么花了这么长时间
我是Eva Azareva
你们需要转移NCIS探员
Victor呢
如果他现在能说话 他会的
她在拖延 但这不是长久之计
She's stalling, but it's not gonna work for long.
你有什么发现
What do you got?
我追踪到了俄罗斯人的手机
I have a trace on the Russian's cell.
好了 正在连接GPS
All right. Connecting to the GPS.
正在获取具体坐标
Getting the exact coordinates now.
找到了 精确的位置 伙计们
There it is. Bull's-eye. Guys!
-伙计们 我们有发现 -好的 Sebastian
- Guys, we got a hit! - Okay, Sebastian.
告诉我们在哪里
Tell us where.
请你小点声告诉我们
And tell us softly, please.
17层
17th floor.
东北侧
Northeast side.
你没事吧
You good?
我没事
I'm good.
怎么这么久才来
What took you so long?
你是真的知道
You do realize it was, like,
17层有很多很多台阶的 对吗
17 freakin' flights of stairs, right?
你知道我已经制服他了 对吗
You know I had him, right?
是啊 你绝对制服他了
Oh, yeah, you definitely had him.
一般人在这时候不是应该说谢谢吗
Don't people usually just say thank you?
哦 不客气
Oh, you're welcome.
我们是不是应该让他继续绑着
Should we leave him tied up?
是
Yes.
特别探员Torres
Special Agent Torres.
很高兴看到你在考验中存活下来了
Glad to see you survived your ordeal.
成功让你自己参与到游戏中
Managed to get yourself in the game.
我说了我讨厌坐在替补席上
I told you I hate riding the bench.
你干得也不错呀
You did good, too.
对新人来说确实不错 对吧
Not bad for a couple of new guys, right?
这虽然不像在厄瓜多尔的监狱里待半年
Well, it's not six months in an Ecuadorian prison
只是为了做好身份 不过
just to set up cover, but, uh,
的确不赖
yeah, not bad.
我五分钟后出发
Shoving off in five.
美丽的夜晚
Beautiful night.
-你会有一段时间看不到了 -是啊
- It'll be your last for a while. - Right.
联邦监狱里没有很多夜间生活
They don't have a lot of night activities in federal prison.
是啊 在你冒险以前
Yeah, well, you should've thought about that
应该考虑到这点才是
before your little adventure.
信不信由你 这和我想的结局
Believe it or not, this is exactly how I thought
一模一样
it would all end.
一切都很值得
And it was completely worth it.
报复值得终身入狱吗
Getting revenge was worth a lifetime in prison?
能遇见你也很棒
Meeting you was nice, too.
真遗憾我们不能
Too bad we won't be able to get
有机会深入了解对方
to know each other a little better...
永不说不
Never say never.
你确定要走吗 你会错过狂欢节的
You sure you got to go? You're gonna miss Mardi Gras.
-现在不就是狂欢节吗 -不 不是
- Hasn't this been Mardi Gras? - No, no, no, no.
这只是狂欢节的前奏
This has been the lead-up to Mardi Gras.
真正的狂欢节是整座城市都在狂欢
Actual Mardi Gras day is when the city really goes off.
哦 你知道 我觉得我已经领教
Oh. You know what, I think I've had my share
新奥尔良的把戏了
of New Orleans shenanigans.
-或许明年吧 -嗯
- Maybe next year. - Mm.
呃
Uh...
你觉得我可不可以 偶尔打给你
you think it's okay if maybe I call you from time to time?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
你刚才问我的方式 有点儿别扭
The way you, uh, just asked me made it sound a little weird.
是这样 我可能会需要一些建议
Well, you know, I just, I might need some advice.
获得未来Sebastian的智慧
Get Future Sebastian's wisdom.
好吧 但你不要再叫我未来Sebastian了
Okay. But you got to stop calling me Future Sebastian.
事实是 你是过去的McGee
The fact is, you are Past McGee.
并且你做得非常棒
And doing a real good job of it.
原来你在这里 McGee
Ah, there you are, McGee.
我刚去车里给Torres送了点吃的
I just dropped some food off with Torres in the car.
-路上可以吃的点心 -非常感谢 谢谢
- A little snack for the road. - Oh, appreciate that. Thank you.
不客气 听着 好好看着Eva
Pleasure. Listen, keep an eye on Eva, okay?
-她可狡猾了 -没问题
- She's tricky. - You got it.
-Jethro -特别探员Pride
- Jethro. - Special Agent Pride.
你应该会很高兴 我把你的队员
You'll be happy to know I'm sending your team home
基本上完好无损地送回去
mostly in one piece.
你们靠自己的力量搞定了 不赖嘛
Eh, you pulled it off on your own. Not bad.
我很高兴 我们没让华盛顿的人
I'm just glad we kept all of official Washington
涌入这个城市
from flooding the city.
是的 至少这次是这样
Yeah. This time, at least.
保持这样吧 你觉得呢
Well, let's keep it that way. What do you say?
当然啦 除非是一次私下拜访
Unless, of course, it's for a social visit.
下次会有别的派对
Next time there's another party,
我可能会直接出现在你面前 给你个惊喜 Dwayne
I might just pop down, surprise you, Dwayne.
这是新奥尔良 兄弟
This is New Orleans, my brother.
各种派对从来不会停
There's always another party going on.
===GA字幕组===
翻译：飞姬、42殿、二f英、小范、二f英、兔姬
校对：师太、流年、风姬
总校：师太
字幕分配&统筹&时间轴：栗子
===本集的标题一定是：断背山下百合花开===
===两个nerd飙科学时旁边两脸懵逼===
===LGBT新时代来临了！===
===Nick感觉很配LaSalle啊===
===同性才是真爱~~===
===Sebastian感觉都要弯掉了===
===爱上Nick 死傲娇===